{
    "id": "c8e7be34cb4945599c864ac50ce2643d",
    "title": "Adjectives Quiz",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Melvin is …………………………. Edwin.",
            "description": "Elder cannot be used predicatively (after a verb).",
            "answers": [
                "elder than",
                "elder to",
                "older than"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dccdefb51ec34923b6b7acf5993894c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is older ………………………….. her husband.",
            "description": "Use than after older.",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "than"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "908bcb0f495c44f5acc01ce067b0fd1d"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is junior ……………………….. me.",
            "description": "The words junior and senior are followed by to.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e03f2aaa039e4afda87a7ea05a3f2890"
        },
        {
            "question": "He earns more than …………………………..",
            "description": "A subject pronoun is unusual after than.",
            "answers": [
                "me",
                "I"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "34e3e8295b2d4d0db38575fc0499e2d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I prefer running ……………………….. jogging.",
            "description": "Prefer should be followed by to.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "over",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4115ce7a32754b39b43a176f8fe2b47b"
        },
        {
            "question": "That was ……………………….. experience in my life.",
            "description": "Worst is the superlative form of bad.",
            "answers": [
                "the worse",
                "the worst",
                "the baddest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5f181ade1811457ab7117c852bf97b82"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am older than ………………………….. is.",
            "description": "We use a subject pronoun after than when the pronoun is followed by a verb. ",
            "answers": [
                "him",
                "he"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b0d7ca192d8a4f559e8209e513711125"
        },
        {
            "question": "I prefer coffee ………………………….. tea.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e5d27f9eea2545129a258831e1061d5a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ………………………… than I am.",
            "description": "Worse is the comparative form of bad.",
            "answers": [
                "worse",
                "worst",
                "bad"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "eab94fe7b03e453e919fb25b53c5096c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Humans are ……………………………. than animals.",
            "description": "The comparative form of intelligent is more intelligent. ",
            "answers": [
                "more intelligent",
                "intelligenter",
                "most intelligent"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0ae80278985f4164ae1865f782ba64cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ……………………………. of the two.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the cleverer",
                "the cleverest",
                "the clever"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d7c7bd772ef74cf2aae7ff9816ec8588"
        },
        {
            "question": "My ………………………….. brother is a soldier.",
            "description": "Elder and older can both be used before nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "elder",
                "older",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2ceb643ae0884ac8b4067ec57d486b71"
        }
    ]
}